When I saw the dragon fruits in the carbon, they
looked very fresh, so I
decided to make jam with them. I don't know if the dragon fruit used in this recipe is not in the jar, the jaggery
powder is not in the jar, and the cardamom powder is
not in the jar, but the pot made by combining these three is
so good that I have to make it again and again
.  The recipe is also simple:
add dragon fruit pieces and jaggery powder, mix them well and
keep stirring on low flame until all three are well infused and reach the consistency of jam.  If you want to
store it in the fridge, you need to
add lemon juice, but if you do this regularly, the
taste will be much better.